From that first trembling step in the hallways of your
dreams. Your heart glided on petals of faith towards
brighter streams. Every step was a chapter
in your
story. Became the anthem of your
glory.
Congratulations, and again we
say. May your tremendous journey light
each day. Roses of Rome we believed
right
from the start. The world has seen your
courage and will hold it in its heart. We
will forever
believe in your dreams.
Through the trials and the triumphs you
stood
unafraid. In the garden of hope, your
foundations were laid. Each challenge a
bridge
to a higher story. Each victory a verse in
the
anthem of your glory.
Congratulations. And again we say.
May your tremendous journey light each
day. Roses of Rome we believed right
from
the start. The world has seen your courage
and will hold it in its heart. We will
forever believe
in your dreams.
We will forever believe in your
dreams. Through the trials and the
triumphs
you stood unafraid. In the garden of hope,
your
foundations were laid. Each challenge a
bridge
to a higher story. Each victory a verse in
the
anthem of your glory. Now the tassel has
turned and the moment has come. Your
tremendous
journey has only begun. Petals of faith
still beneath your feet guiding each step
until dreams are complete.
We cheer you. The world hears your name.
And roses of rome will always
proclaim. Oh, we
will,  believe in your
dreams.